var data = [{
	"question":"The absorption of ink by blotting paper involves",
	"a":"viscosity of ink",
	"b":"capillary action phenomenon",
	"c":"diffusion of ink through the blotting",
	"d":"siphon action",
	"ans":"b"
},{
	"question":"Nuclear sizes are expressed in a unit named",
	"a":"Fermi",
	"b":"Angstrom",
	"c":"Newton",
	"d":"Tesla",
	"ans":"a"
},{
	"question":"Light year is a unit of",
	"a":"time",
	"b":"distance",
	"c":"light",
	"d":"intensity of light",
	"ans":"b"
},{
	"question":"g=____",
	"a":"9.8 m/s",
	"b":"980 m/m",
	"c":"98 m/ms",
	"d":"9.8 cm/s",
	"ans":"a"
},{
	"question":"Light from the Sun reaches us in nearly",
	"a":"2 mins",
	"b":"4 mins",
	"c":"8 mins",
	"d":"16 mins",
	"ans":"c"
},{
	"question":"Pa(Pascal) is the unit for",
	"a":"Thrust",
	"b":"Pressure",
	"c":"Frequency",
	"d":"Conductivity",
	"ans":"b"
},{
	"question":"Pick out the scalar quantity",
	"a":"Force",
	"b":"Pressure",
	"c":"Velocity",
	"d":"Acceleration",
	"ans":"b"
},{
	"question":"Magnetism at the centre of a bar magnet is",
	"a":"Minimum",
	"b":"Maximum",
	"c":"Zero",
	"d":"Maximum or Minimum",
	"ans":"c"
},{
	"question":"Of the following properties of a wave, the one that is independent of the other is its",
	"a":"amplitude",
	"b":"velocity",
	"c":"wavelength",
	"d":"frequency",
	"ans":"a"
},{
	"question":"Lux is the SI unit of",
	"a":"intensity of illumination",
	"b":"luminous efficiency",
	"c":"luminous flux",
	"d":"luminous intensity",
	"ans":"a"
}]